Guide to the INDUSCO Inc. Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Oversized Items
  - CIC product labels, announcements, insignia, sample invoices, display and promotional materials, in Chinese and English, 1939-1950. (Box Flat Box)
    (See I.B.3)
  - Photographs (Box Flat Box)
    (See I.B.4.. Includes: One scrapbook on Bailie Schools. General photographs arranged by subject, Mounted photographs by Ayscough, Florence--40 enlarged photographs with captions not related to CIC, and several hundred mounted photographs of CIC activities, with captions, for exhibit purposes. Most are enlargements of photographs in I.B.4)
  - Posters (Box Flat Box)
    Set of thirteen original display posters, each bearing a textile sample, photographs, and captions, representing the different stages of blanket production from wool selection and processing through the collection of the finished product by the army, (See I.B.4) b. Two oversized design books for textiles, produced and published by the CIG Institute, Ghengtu, 1944. See I.B.I Institute for GIG, Textiles)
  - Art work (Box Flat Box)
    ( includes 19 original brush-and-ink drawings by Jack Chan produced to resist Japanese aggression, support CIC. These drawings were first reproduced in The China Weekly Review and later appeared in two booklet editions published in Hongkong and New York. Also includes Shantan Bailie School student art work)
  - Daily Record of Cash Received, November 28, 1940 (Box Flat Box)
    (See II.B Finances.)
- Series VI: Miscellaneous Correspondence and Other Files
  - Rewi Alley (Box 176)
  - Hugh Deane: Correspondence, memos, minutes, printed materials, 1939-1943 1980-1985 (Box 177)
    (includes files on revival of CIC in 1980s)
- Series VII: Photographs and Slides
  - Negative Files, 2 card file boxes and Slide Show with commentary (Box 178-179)
    (commentary for the slide show available in the repository)
- Series VIII: Elizabeth Schiffman Files
  - Publications
    - General Publications (Box 180)
    - Indusco Publications (Box 180)
    - Indusco Bulletin, 1942-1950, (2 folders) (Box 180)
    - Publications and Articles, (3 folders) (Box 181)
      (Articles written by or about Indusco in magazines and journals)
    - Newsletters (Box 181)
  - Elizabeth Schiffman Files, 1942-1946 (Box 181)
    (Primarily material related to the Publicity Committee, including reports, memos, and correspondence)
  - Photographs (Box 181)